what sort of questions or answers there
you go good idea yeah what we're back at
the camera again what's going on we must
have done something right okay did it
again there was there was some
discussion about working out what the
Suzuki was doing there's been a few
questions or a few people have answered
it but not necessarily correct so did
you want to let them know anything at
all or just from keeping in the dark
never tell anybody what you come up with
because doesn't do you any good if you
have for ego tree and you hand on what
you found you got nothing
yeah if you have for praise and glory
it's the same thing as you go through
well you haven't got anything then right
and who do you give it to you see just
with the water stuff and everything else
it's separating water minerals and
everything else your best physicists and
water board people everything else
believe that they got already all the
answers there's no new things to learn
the magnetic people say this no
things too low and they've got
everything okay
so within cars swimming I came here with
cars and everything else they just don't
run the way that you think you've
already put a heap up on this weapon
internet about me and everything else on
on stuff about the battery you write the
spark Wow
the installations which aren't okay and
then you went and you paid the guy for
esa's uki I was only pissing him off
because he thought he knew everything
tomatoes and so on and $400 Suzuki
import' wente $6,000 on a for sale
straight after because you can turn
everything off I'm still guys yeah they
do I take that but you had a paying 50
bucks with a no I did he wouldn't give
it even say the idea and that wasn't
really for anybody or anything else or
to tell anybody the best thing is it was
the piece of guy off we thought he knew
every damn thing yeah and now he's run
the pasture all the fame and
electrician's he could run the past they
he's chased up every wiring diagram that
he can off the computer because there's
where he goes all the time no they give
me their mobile things and so on and he
couldn't figure out what's happened and
apparently say what good is a do I tell
them anybody what you've done when your
mechanics engineers physicists
electricians magnetism people all your
top scientists and everything else Rick
and you're full of anyway we know
that we leave anything right ok so you
guys this isn't Joe this is this is just
an illusion
I mean all those things so what are you
gonna do we understand again so all the
oil companies with a flame and they
shoot me in two people just refuge ops
or oil where they gonna it's not fear
it's not paranoia it's just you know
cause the Gulf War and everything else a
few drops of oil yeah then they didn't
find any think they're blaming me for
everything anyway set fire to all the
oil wells near you
going up and smoke still today well good
is it but they've set you up to run cars
off oil petrol the Jordan petrol today
one drop of oil in it it's not where
it's come from
so what's all the prices all got to do
with it okay but you're running on
methanol alcohols flame and all these
other things in the war you had all
these other different things you could
run the vehicles off you know when you
get desperate enough they find them then
they go in variant so it's a very all
that technology were they gonna do to me
yep six foot under or mark might a
little bit further Jack hey can I have
to say it look frequencies and
everything else you've been there you
heard a bit Peters put to you and
everything gets its assistant because
that run off the petrol you don't run
off the spark just combinations of them
set up a fuel before but you can you've
heard a pre-ignition a cold evening I've
described that before they run with the
key turn off your timing tell you want
to bring it back into where you had it
with a key on did you see their advance
or you your timing and it stops
all that you ever try gone the other way
you see that's not what this is okay
that's not with all the other stuff
that's just cars run you know we're
gonna follow here just now if you're
looking at it who just got shut down
because you got a couple of you had a
magnetic car was just all over the news
in the papers and there he goes in tell
me had a magnetic car and they
demonstrate near he only got a couple of
flaming investors front of you but over
a million all right I don't know all the
details I'm not part of it so yeah this
guy run they proved it one of them
whether it was a setup or not and
everything else we don't know yet but
one of the guys who only put a couple of
thousand dollars you know some more that
says what this is well just prove the
whole lot and everything else I want me
money back and I reckon
so full of but he already seen the
vehicle the vehicles being sent out of
Australia for for payments and
everything else but it was raining but
where'd your first guy come in Henry
Ford wasn't Henry Ford run on magnetic
fighters you know no he could throw away
the fuel wasn't Hitler running these
Volkswagens wagons you don't know about
it the desert without fuel
anybody's outfield well usually I'll
fuel out there we'd you'll incoming fury
out there you've got thousands and
thousands of gallons of fuel flavor in
the desert to what they like to cold
well I'd say they put a living what they
do with a fuel it took Lydia all right
you got back the fuels with that run but
now they're getting really smart and
everything else because they've got
computers in do over the mechanic okay
the overrides all there is the electrics
and systems what you can change and I
want you to know that but your your
engine today really is virtually right
back to the very first engine with
absolutely zero on it nothing to run
they all make me do things you do when
you go sucker I can't be like that
it's all these and what's all the rest
of the stuff when you lift a bowling yet
ah can I get a hand around it well
that's to stop that from doing something
and that's stop that one from doing that
and that's just not that from doing
something else and all of the time the
cord and what's your computer for stop
are you doing anything and the mechanic
ever do anything it's how it's all
regulated and how do you if your
computer gets out and everything else if
you remove it just to give you this how
do you said your computer how do you do
your mechanics on your car when it's not
running properly well you don't need
pathologist has a box what's that it's a
frequency but we some numbers in a book
which says you know this number here it
goes for that then they take I rent say
he plugs it into the plug on the
computer
oh no that's he out of alignment press
press press press put the frequency back
again away you go that's where all that
works and you didn't
don't anybody think of that it's all
these frequencies it's and with just
electrics it's all just some number
system to put it back in
same is turn your TV different station
different frequency radio station same
thing it's all these all I did to it
Suzuki I change the frequency now don't
need the petrol runners they need this
back and it don't need the key
it's still booted about truck what when
you turn it off they're on one occasion
still got booted yeah well you go out
and hang on to a sparkplug leader
anything else only you know that turn
the key off the electronics and
everything else a big jazz ivory teeth I
turn the key off all right
also you wanna hang on that when they
turned on it so why did the color of the
spark change color yellow smart guy when
it was rigged up disappeared we did the
where did the fogging of the old man ago
with the Bell hailing yeah where did
that guy